<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MrFCode Blog</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on MrFCode Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>ABOUT I&amp;rsquo;m Irfan,
I am just a young student who started programming at the age of 14. I started with HTML, CSS, and JS. Now in 2025, I learned Linux, Python, C++, and Bash script. I have also done some CTF challenges on HackTheBox, TryHackMe, PicoCTF, OverTheWire, and CTFLearn.
I have never taken my computer science subject in high school or followed any paid course. I just learned all of this on my own just through the open-source information on the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/posts/blogsetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/blogsetup/</guid>
      <description>23-03-2025
Blog Setup with hugo in Ubuntu (Linux) From Mark Down (.md) file into website Required to be installed  Go, Git, DartSass  First open terminal &amp;amp; Install git and go sudo apt update &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sudo apt install git golang-go -y
Getting started   Install hugo from the official website. Download from here
  Then check the version if you have download it correctly by typing hugo version</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/posts/ctf/thm/silverplatter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ctf/thm/silverplatter/</guid>
      <description>CTF Silver Platter - TryHackMe 24-03-2025
Starting with nmap  Scanning the target to identify open ports  $sudo nmap -T5 -Pn -oN nmap/init 10.10.126.96
# Nmap 7.94SVN scan initiated Mon Mar 24 06:40:27 2025 as: nmap -T5 -Pn -oN nmap/init 10.10.126.96 Warning: 10.10.126.96 giving up on port because retransmission cap hit (2). Nmap scan report for 10.10.126.96 Host is up (0.21s latency). Not shown: 997 closed tcp ports (reset) PORT STATE SERVICE 22/tcp open ssh 80/tcp open http 8080/tcp open http-proxy # Nmap done at Mon Mar 24 06:40:40 2025 -- 1 IP address (1 host up) scanned in 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/posts/docker101/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/docker101/</guid>
      <description>How to run Linux using Docker 2025-03-24
Install docker on your linux ( For windows users can follow along with WSL (Windows Subsystem for Linux). ) sudo apt update &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sudo install docker.io -y
Then install an linux image by using this command: ( Search More Images ) sudo docker pull ubuntu:latest
 make sure use the &amp;lsquo;:latest&amp;rsquo; in the end of image name so you get the latest version then just wait for the installation to finish.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
